[
    {  
        "question": "What year did 2Pac died?",
        "answers": ["1995","1997","1994","1996"],
        "correct_answer": "1996",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "What is 2Pac's first song?",
        "answers": ["Hit 'Em Up","Trapped","I Don't Give a Fuck","Same Song"],
        "correct_answer": "Same Song",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Calvin Cordozar Broadus is the name of which rap artist?",
        "answers": ["2Pac","Ice Cube","Snoop Dogg","Dr. Dre"],
        "correct_answer": "Snoop Dogg",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "What rapper was supposed to play the role of Jody in movie Baby Boy?",
        "answers": ["Kurupt","Ice Cube","Eazy-E","2Pac"],
        "correct_answer": "2Pac",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Who was not a member of N.W.A?",
        "answers": ["MC Ren","Ice Cube","Eazy-E","Spice 1"],
        "correct_answer": "Spice 1",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "What label did Suge Knight and Dr. Dre start?",
        "answers": ["Death Row","Ruthless Records","Interscope","Aftermath"],
        "correct_answer": "Death Row",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Which rapper released the hit single Gin and Juice in the 90s?",
        "answers": ["Snoop Dogg", "Ice Cube", "2Pac", "Eazy-E"],
        "correct_answer": "Snoop Dogg",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Which hip hop artist released the album All Eyez on Me in 1996?",
        "answers": ["2Pac", "Snoop Dogg", "Ice Cube", "Dr. Dre"],
        "correct_answer": "2Pac",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Finish the lyrics: \"It was a clear black night...\"",
        "answers": ["just hit the Eastside of LBC", "a clear white moon", "I was looking for some fool", "turning a gat full"],
        "correct_answer": "a clear white moon",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Name a song: \"Just waking in the morning gotta thank God...\"",
        "answers": ["It Was a Good Day","Who Am I","Regulate","Check Yo Self"],
        "correct_answer": "It Was a Good Day",
        "difficulty": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "What was Eazy-E's cause of death?",
        "answers": ["Murder","Natural","AIDS","He is still alive"],
        "correct_answer": "AIDS",
        "difficulty": 1
    }
]